Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sports Information Office records
1932-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Sports Information Office
UA.13.02.0001
320 Linear Feet
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. The collection contains press releases, photographs, audio reels, and other material pertaining to sports at Duke University. The date ranges from 1932-ongoing.
Access Restrictions
Access note. Collection contains electronic records that must be requested through the collection guide and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Provenance
The Sports Information Office records were received by the University Archives as a transfer over time.
Historical Note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the Sports Information Office has maintained records, photographs and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
This collection includes press releases, photographs, clippings, scrapbooks, plaques, audio reels and other material pertaining to sports at Duke University. Topics range from individual sports (badminton, boxing, high school basketball) and the coaching school to freshmen sports. For ease of patron use, individual collections have been created for the bulk of sport-specific information. For example, there is a separate finding aid for both men and women's basketball, football, and baseball. Please see the list of Related Collections below for a comprehensive list. The collection ranges in date from 1932-ongoing.
Accessions after 2012 have been added as separate series. These accessions include materials on the Men's Basketball Championships in 1991, 1992, 2001, 2010, and 2015, as well as many other materials covering athletics at Duke.
Related Material
Baseball Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Cross Country and Track and Field Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Fencing Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Field Hockey Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Football Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Golf Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Gymnastics Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Lacrosse Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Men's Basketball Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Rowing Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Soccer Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Swimming and Diving Team Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Tennis Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Volleyball Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Women's Basketball Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Wrestling Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
Duke University -- Sports; Duke University. Sports Information Office
- General Files, 1932-1991, 6 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes general files created by the Sports Information Office. It includes largely press releases but also clippings and files on high school basketball.
  - Badminton Championships Program, Cameron Indoor Stadium, April 1942 (Box 1)
  - Badminton National championships, 1942 (Box 1)
  - Boxing, 1932-1936 (Box 1)
  - Boxing, 1937-1940 (Box 1)
  - Charlotte Feature on Simons, Muse, and Chapman, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Coaching School, 1932-1935 (Box 1)
  - Coaching School, 1936-1940 (Box 1)
  - Composite spring Sports Schedules and Releases, 1956-1973 (17 folders) (Box 1)
  - Director: Correspondence, circa 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - Football: General Stories, early 1940s (Box 1)
  - Freshmen Sports, 1933-1935 (Box 2)
  - Freshmen Sports, 1936-1939 (Box 2)
  - Freshmen Sports, 1948-1951 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Softball, 1933, 1949, undated (Box 2)
  - Intramurals, 1932-1947 (Box 2A)
  - Register and Press Releases, 1933-1935 (Box 2A)
  - Register and Press Releases, 1936-1939 (Box 2A)
  - Register and Press Releases, 1939-1943 (Box 3)
  - Register and Press Releases, 1946-1949 (Box 3)
  - Spring Sports/Press Releases, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Spring Sports/Press Releases, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Spring Sports/Press Releases, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1973 May-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1974 Jan.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1975 Jan.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1976 Jan.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1977 Jan.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1978 Jan.-June (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1978 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1979 Jan.-June (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1979 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1980 Jan.-June (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1980 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1981 Jan.-June (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1981 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1982 Jan.-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Press Releases, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Southern High School Basketball Tournament, 1939-1946 (Box 5)
  - Southern High School, N.C. State High School Basketball Tournaments, circa 1940s (Box 5)
  - A Story of Glory, Ted Mann: Notes, correspondence, clippings (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - A Story of Glory, Final Manuscript (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - Summer School Sports, 1935; undated (Box 6)
  - Summaries and Miscellaneous, 1932-1934 (Box 6)
  - Track-Lacrosse-Crew, pre-1980 (Box 6)
  - Women's Athletics, 1973-1976 (Box 6)
  - Women's Schedules and Intercollegiates, pre-1980 (Box 6)
- Memorabilia and Oversize Material (including oversize photographs), 1937-1995, 5 boxes
  This series contains oversize photograhs (some of which are mounted), oversize printed material, plaques, and scrapbooks.
  - Hall of Fame Bowl Plaque, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Color photograph from The Herald Sun of "The Shot," Basketball, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Final Four Minneapolis Pins (2), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Lacrosse, vol. 9, no. 2 (Jack Persons article), 1985 April (Box 7)
  - Signed broadside of Ben Bennett's ACC Record, circa 1983 (Box 7)
  - Facsimile of basketball team caricatures, undated (Box 7)
  - NCAA Basketball Media information, 1986 (Box 7)
  - World Top 20 Poll plaque, 1979 Dec. 17 (Box 7)
  - Ed Koffenberger, All-American, unmounted image, 1947 (Box 8)
  - Mounted images of the following All-American basketball players:
    - Ed Koffenberger (1946, 1947) (Box 8)
    - Dick Groat (1951, 1952) (Box 8)
    - Jeff Mullins (1964) (Box 8)
    - Jack Marin (1966) (Box 8)
    - Bob Verga (1966, 1967) (Box 8)
    - Mike Lewis (1968) (Box 8)
  - All-American certificates for baseball players:
    - Dick Groat (1952) (Box 8)
    - William Werber, Jr. (1952, 1954) (Box 8)
    - Albert Spangler (1954) (Box 8)
  - Oversize images of All-American football players and superlatives
    - Woody Lipscomb (1937) (Box 8)
    - Dan Hill, Jr. (1938) (Box 8)
    - Pat Preston (1943) (Box 8)
    - Bill Millner (1943, 1946) (Box 8)
    - Billy Cox (1950) (Box 8)
    - Jack Kistler (1951) (Box 8)
    - Red Smith (1951) (Box 8)
    - Dwight Bumgarner (1960) (Box 8)
    - Jean Berry (1962 (Box 8)
    - Jean Berry (1962) and Jay Wilkinson (1963) (Box 8)
    - Bob Matheson (1966) (Box 8)
  - AACBC District 3 Champs plaque, 1961 (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Art Gregory, Order of the Ahepa Athletic Hall of Fame plaque, 1981 (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Eddie Cameron resolution, 1972 (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Big Four Basketball Tournament Champs plaque, 1979-1980 (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Stanley Schneider and Leonard Merl plaque, early 1980s (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Rose Bowl Scrapbook, 1942 (Box 10)
  - Scrapbook - Football, 1970; Basketball, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
- Media Guides and Publicity 1985-2000, 6 boxes
  - Fencing (Box 12)
  - Men's Swimming (Box 12)
  - Women's Swimming (Box 12)
  - Men's Tennis (Box 12)
  - Rowing (Box 12)
  - Women's Lacrosse (Box 13)
  - Men's Soccer (Box 14)
  - Men's Golf (Box 15)
  - Track and Field (Men and Women) (Box 15)
  - Women's Soccer (Box 15)
  - Baseball (Box 15)
  - Misc./General (Box 16)
  - Women's Tennis (Box 16)
  - Wrestling (Box 16)
  - Field Hockey (Box 16)
  - Men's Lacrosse (Box 16)
  - Volleyball (Box 17)
  - Women's Golf (Box 17)
- Sound Recordings, 1982-1985, undated, 5 boxes
  This series contains radio station broadcasts of Duke University football and basketball games recorded on 1/4 tape on 10-inch reels. Not all reels are labeled and not all distinguish between football and basketball.
  - Unlabeled, 1982 July 19 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Tennessee, 1982 Sept. 4 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Navy, 1982 Sept. 19 (2 reels) (Box 18)
  - Duke/Clemson, 1982 Oct. 16 (Box 18)
  - Duke/UNC, 1982 Nov. (2 reels) (Box 18)
  - Duke/ECU, 1982 Nov. 27 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Appalachian State, 1982 Nov. 30 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Colorado, 1982 Dec. 2 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Virginia, 1982 Dec. 8 (Box 18)
  - Duke/New Hampshire, 1982 Dec. 29 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Wagner, 1983 Jan. 5 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Lasalle, 1983 Jan. 8 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Louisville, 1983 Jan. 12 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Maryland, 1983 Jan. 15 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Wake Forest, 1983 Jan. 19 (Box 19)
  - Duke/UNC, 1983 Jan. 22 (Box 19)
  - Duke/NC State, 1983 Jan. 26 (Box 19)
  - Duke/William & Mary, 1983 Feb. 2 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Georgia Tech, 1983 Feb. 9 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Stetson, 1983 Feb. 16 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Wake Forest, 1983 Feb. 19 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Maryland, 1983 Feb. 21 (Box 19)
  - Duke/NC State, 1983 Feb. 23 (Box 19)
  - Unlabeled, 1983 Feb. 26 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Clemson, 1983 March 2 (Box 19)
  - Duke/UNC, 1983 March 5 (2 reels) (Box 20)
  - ACC Tournament: First half of NC State/Wake Forest, 1983 March 11 (Box 20)
  - ACC Tournament: Second half of NC State/Wake Forest; part of Duke/Virginia, 1983 March 11 (Box 20)
  - ACC Tournament: End of Duke/Virginia; all of Maryland/Georgia Tech, 1983 March 11 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Indiana, 1984 Sept. 8 (2 reels) (Box 20)
  - Duke/Army, 1984 Sept. 29 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Virginia, 1984 Oct. 6 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Virginia Tech, 1984 Oct. 13 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Clemson, 1984 Oct. 20 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Maryland, 1984 Oct. 27 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Georgia Tech, 1984 Nov. 3 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Athletes in Action, 1984 Nov. 14 (Box 21)
  - Duke/NCSU (football), 1984 Nov. 17 (Box 21)
  - Duke/UNC (football), 1984 Nov. 24 (Box 21)
  - Duke/St. Louis, 1984 Nov. 26 (Box 21)
  - Duke/William & Mary, 1984 Nov. 28 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Appalachian State, 1984 Dec. 5 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Virginia, 1984 Dec. 8 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Davidson, 1984 Dec. 17 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Southwestern, 1984 Dec. 19 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Univ. of Alabama-Birmingham, 1984 Dec. 28 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Southern California, 1984 Dec. 29 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Virginia, 1985 Jan. 5 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Wake Forest, 1985, Nov. 10 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Wake Forest, undated (Box 22)
  - Georgia Tech/Virginia, undated (Box 22)
  - UNC/NC State, undated (Box 22)
  - Virginia/NC State, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Duke/Colorado, reel 2, undated (Box 22)
- UA1990-0061
  - NCAA Track and Field Reel 1, 1990 (Box 335, Video-reel UA13020001-Vid1-0001)
  - NCAA Track and Field Reel 2, 1990 (Box 335, Video-reel UA13020001-Vid1-0002)
- UA2013-0034, 1927-2015
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access note. Collection contains electronic records that must be requested through the collection guide and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions. Access note. Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
  Scope and Contents
  This accession contains a large amount of material covering several decades and multiple sports, and includes clippings and other materials related to the 1991, 1992, and 2001 Men's Basketball Championships, as well as many individual player files.
  - Men's Lacrosse: Vekstein, Andrew, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
    Access note. Collection contains electronic records that must be requested through the collection guide and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
    Also includes digital disk.
  - Men's Lacrosse: Costabile, CJ, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Turri, Justin, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Coyle, Stephen, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Belmont, Ben, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Manley, Michael, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Rock, Mike, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Rullan, Andrew, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Shannon, Christopher, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Rontanz, Rob, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Meyer, Scot, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Golf: Clippings, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Wrestling: Harding, Ryan, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Wrestling: Benecomo, Diego, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Wrestling: Terrezza, Peter, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Wrestling: Fulk, Andrew, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Soccer: Morales, Andrew, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Basketball, March-April 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Men's Basketball: Recruits, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Tennis: NCAA Tournament, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Tennis: Game Notes, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Tennis: ACC Releases, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Tennis: Box Scores, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Tennis: Releases, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Tennis: Team Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Golf, 2007-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer, 2007-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Basketball, 2007-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Rankings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Photos, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Photos, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Tournaments, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Games, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Rankings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Photos, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Clippings, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: College Cup and Photos, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Publications, circa 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: NCAA Polls ACC Box Scores, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Soccer: Releases, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Stat Sheets, ACC, Releases, Polls, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Golf: Results, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Basketball: Results, NCAA ACC Releases, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Women's Basketball: Polls, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Field Hockey, 2002; 5 folders (Box UA2013-0034.3)
  - Men's Soccer, 2002; 3 folders (Box UA2013-0034.3)
  - Men's Soccer: Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.3)
  - Men's Soccer, 1986-1987 (Box UA2013-0034.3)
  - Wrestling, 2001-2002; 26 folders (Box UA2013-0034.3)
  - Swimming and Diving: Results, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.3)
  - Swimming, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Swimming: Team Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Swimming and Diving: Recruits, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Swimming and Diving: ACC Releases, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Baseball: Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Baseball: Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Baseball: Notes, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Baseball: Clippings, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Men and Women's Lacrosse: Guides, 2003-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Baseball: Statistics and Guides, 2005-2006; 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Football Yearbook, 2000 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Football: Photo Order forms, circa 2002-2013; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Negatives, 1991-1992; 2 folders; Mold on materials. (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1991-1992; Mold on materials. (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, 1989-1990; Mold on materials. (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets/Composites, 1990-1991; 2 folders; Mold on materials. (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Men's Basketball: National Championship Slides, 1991-1992; Mold on materials. (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Men's Basketball: Contact Sheets, circa 2002-2013; Mold on materials. (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Men's Basketball: Final Four Trophies-Slides, circa 2002-2013; Mold on materials. (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1989-1990; Mold on materials. (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Women's Soccer: Clippings, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Golf: NCAA Tournament, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Shelby Shay, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament: 1st (Samford) and 2nd Round (Vanderbilt), March 18, 2012; March 20, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State ACC Tournament Quarterfinals, 2012-03-02 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Rankings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Blue/White Scrimmage, 2012-10-28 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Shaw; Duke vs. Queens, October 30, 2012; November 4, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Presbyterian; Duke vs. Iona, November 17-18, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Valparaiso; Duke vs. Xavier, November 23, 2012; November 25, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan; Duke vs. California, November 28, 2012; December 2, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech; Duke vs St. John's, December 6, 2012; December 9, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. CSU--Bakersfield; Duke vs. Southern California, December 21, 2012; December 22, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Monmoth; Duke vs. NC State, December 30, 2012; January 3, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. Clemson, January 6, 2013; January 10, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
    Includes 29 digital disks, processed by Digital Records Archivist.
  - Women's Golf: Photos, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
    Includes 5 digital disks, processed by Digital Records Archivist.
  - Women's Soccer: Photos, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Track and Field: Photos and Media Guide, 1998-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Track and Field: Photos and Media Guide, 2000-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Track and Field: Photos and Media Guide, 1999-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Men's/Women's Cross Country: Results, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Track and Field, 2002; 28 folders (Box UA2013-0034.8)
  - Men's Cross Country, 2001-2002; 11 folders (Box UA2013-0034.8)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2002; 13 folders (Box UA2013-0034.8)
  - Wrestling, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.8)
  - Duke Wrestling Program, 1993-1994 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guides, 1967; 1970-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Schedule, 1967-1968 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, 1980-1981 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, 1982-1983 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, 1983-1984 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, 1984-1985 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, 1985-1986 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, 1986-1987 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, 1987-1988 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling: Media Guide, 1988-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling Media Guide, 1990-1991 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling Program, 1992-1993 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling Program, 1991-1992 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling Program, 1995-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling Program, 1994-1995 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling Program, 1996-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Harvey Schedules, circa 1980-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, circa 1980-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1978-1983 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1984-1987 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1988-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1989-1993 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1993-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Tournament Documents, circa 1980-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: ACC Results, circa 1980-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: NCAA Weight Certification, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Athlete Insurance Information, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling: Program Materials, circa 2004-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling: Competition Entry and Weight Certification, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling: ELITE Camp, 2007; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling: Program Materials, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling: ACC, 1987 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling: Weight Certification, 2003-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Department of Intercollegiate Athletics--Staff Handbook, circa 2003-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling: Program Materials, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling: Tournaments, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1983-1984 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1973-1974 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos and Clippings, 1980-1981 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos and Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box UA2013-0034.12)